Nooooooooooooooo!
Hahaha!
Yeah, I'm gonna keep these for you.
You meanie!
You jump scare me by showing up
then rip away something I love!
That's it, they're yours now!
It'll be hard for you, but it's
for your own good, alright sis?
See you later.
She's crying like a cat that's
been locked out in the rain.
No, I can't give in this time.
I'm sure she'll understand eventually.
But maybe taking all of
them at once was too harsh.
I should just give her back one box.
Hey, I was...
Ha ha, the removal was a success!
Soon as I heard Emocha was coming over,
I put the ol' thinking cap
on and got to swallow it.
Lighter, lighter, where's my...
Look at you with the save.
me me me Thank you.
I know this is random, it's just,
I've wanted to get something off my
chest, but it's easier if we're alone.
Oh.
Well, listen, I guess you could
tell I've had a big crush on you.
Like a really big crush, Imoko.
And if we get married one day, hey.
Oh, um, thank you for saying that.
But I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Come on man don't let this get to you
if I had better here she would have
said yes dude you're Gonna bounce
back there are so many girls out there
man I like her she was it she was my
soul Man whoa whoa whoa dude unbelievable
imoko this imoko that shouldn't
seem that special to me Don't fall,
don't fall.
Seriously?
Would you watch where you're going?
Sorry.
I mean, are you blind or what?
That's enough, Mikoto.
Do you really need to
talk to her that way?
But I was just...
Imoko, are you okay?
Yeah.
Here, I'll help you.
Oh, thank you.
Sorry about Mikoto.
What the hell?
Solve it.
Even I know that I'm being a awful person.
I'm horrible.
I'm just not sure how
else I'm supposed to act,
but I feel like my head's
probably messed up all the time.
I'm here for you, and I know
you'll get through this.
How about some Yonadas before we go home?
Okay, but you're buying.
You're buying, right?
Wait so why did you turn
him down he's a pretty
nice guy and you said
he's cute he's hot right
You could have at least given
him a chance don't you think
I don't know how to say this
it's just that I feel like
he's too well put together
does that make Make sense?
Kinda.
I can't believe you hit them again.
You can't keep these ones either.
They've got to be right
there like three cigarettes!
No!
This is ridiculous.
You do realize that you would
never last on your own, right?
Shadesmoker Cat!
Welcome in.
Can I take care of my health
insurance premium? Sure.
And one...
number 12. Yes!
So what did you order?
A Chikawa cheeseburger and a Nyamu shake.
Thank you, Bispo coupon, for the half off.
I have a Chikawa cheeseburger
and a Nyamu shake.
Order number 12.
That's my order.
Yes!
So sorry about that.
But if I was embarrassed,
I'm sure you were too.
It's fine.
I've gotten used to being
embarrassed by you, Yaku.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
Thing is, I was called
by a number for so long.
Anytime I hear that
number, I can't help it.
I just react.
Four times three is 12.
Then another 12. Yes!
Math class must have really
sucked for you, huh? Not really.
Elementary school was actually okay.
It happened when I was
a bit older. Oh, gotcha.
Ooh, a teacher.
I like the sound of that.
Wait, I forgot that Beast
Folk can't become teachers.
I guess part-timer it is, then.
I'm gonna be a lawyer.
You think Beast Folk can be lawyers?
Try again, part-timer for you, too.
All right, I'm gonna be a doctor.
Muddy, here I come.
Doctors are off limits, too.
How the hell's a Beast Folk supposed
to make a living in this world?
This game sure is vintage, huh?
We're all part-timers
whether we like it or not.
The Beast Folk Life
game is fun because it's
completely different from the real world.
Oh, guess I'm a scholar.
Wanna bet we can't be that either?
That's a good guess.
Yeah, except I chose to be a human.
So now you've got a
problem being a Beast Folk?
Uh, I...
does it really even matter
this is just a game?
A game that I'm kicking your asses at.
The smart move is to cough up the
cash and move to Machida right away.
You're up to your neck and dip now.
When you reach the goal,
your debt goes away.
So the more in the hole
you are, the better.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Ooh, it's time to get married!
Wonder what my partner's species is.
Looks like a bespoke marriage for me.
After you're married, you find
out what species they are?
Now that seems silly.
I'm walking down the aisle with a
human, so it looks like, yay, money!
Sounds like true love.
Hey, I'm marrying a human, too!
I'm marrying a beast folk.
Wait, let's see what happens when
a human marries a beast folk.
Here, Yaku, read it. Huh?
What is this?
If you're a human in this game,
stay away from beast folk.
There are many differences
compared to humans.
Huh.
Many times,
beast folk are physically superior to
humans in speed, agility, and hunting.
Beast folk excel in underwater mobility,
and when damp, their scent
can be highly addictive.
As beast folk age, they retain
a very youthful appearance.
They meow.
They can trigger cat allergies.
And if either of the parents is a beast
folk, the child will always be one.
Yeah, it's definitely an old game.
Or a horror movie.
Next turn, that bullseye is mine. Already?
I'm on fire!
Oh, yeah, friendly reminder the main
goal in this game is to die not live.
That's a little creepy The
point is you want to die
happy So basically one full
round is equal to one year.
That means Yanni died
when she was 11 years old
I'm gonna give that smoking a break.
All right, it's my turn
Okay, I spent a 12
Chainsmoker!
Huh?
Where are you going?
Out to catch beetles again?
Not weird at all!
You're like a little kid!
I'm loving your buck-catching uniform!
I have an idea.
On my stream,
I'll tell a story about
a 20-year-old jobless
beesfolk looking for
beetles instead of a job.
Then I'll come with you and...
Yakup?
You're looking for beetles?
Sorry, but I don't got a minute to spare.
That's a lie.
I just don't feel like going.
Sorry, hon.
Are you all alone?
Is Yaniko...
Oh, she was starting a part-time job.
And then I'm pretty sure Tatsuro
had some impossible work deadline.
Mariko's been drinking all day.
Oh, it's not safe for a young
lady to go into the woods alone,
so be careful out there, you hear? Okay.
She got fired from a
part-time job, didn't she?
I guess she's still upset about it.
Sorry.
I would have gone, but there's
a neighborhood meeting today.
You gonna be okay on
your own? I'll be fine.
I have my cell phone with me.
Well, you're a pretty tough kid, Yaku.
Just watch yourself, okay?
Yaku, listen.
If you really can't find anything,
then just let me know, all right?
Seriously, I'll be fine.
This is just a little
unexpected vacation is all.
Thanks for worrying about me, though.
Hmm.
Huh?
Oh, uh, hey, Yanni Neko. Hmm?
What's up, Yaku?
Thought you had a part-time gig.
More like part-time crap.
They said smoking was
allowed during the interview,
but when the smoking
area is under renovation,
suddenly smoking is a no-no.
So I bounced.
Are you going to work
right now or something?
Uh, no.
I'm going to catch some beetles.
I'm free, so how about I come with you?
Okay.
So, do beetles taste good or what?
Huh?
No, I don't eat them.
You mean you're collecting
them just for fun?
Well, I'm looking for stag beetles,
and they're actually pretty cool.
If you say so.
Hello to my Hame channel, subscribers!
Today I have a fun surprise!
I'm here in the unexplored forest where
the Alpha is rumored to be living!
What's the Alpha?
You don't know about this?
They're the beast folk who
rule this whole region.
Oh yeah, do you remember that stuff
we smoked that got you really high?
These cigarettes?
The Alphas actually grow
the leaves for these.
Those were really smooth.
Yeah, I know.
Most of the ones I've run into are really
nice, so they'll give you some if you ask.
Oh, here we are.
Special zone number six, one
of the alpha tobacco villages.
Wow!
It's like the Jomon period!
Ah, Yaku, you've returned to us.
And you brought a few companions I see.
Hey there, chief!
Good to see you.
She's The big shot who pretty much
runs everything around the village.
And I'm Yanni.
Hmm.
I'm the chief here.
Lani, our home welcomes you.
I'm sorry for just dropping by.
I was hoping my friends and I could
partake of some of your tobacco.
Mm. Hmm.
This year's harvest is upon us.
The leaves are plentiful, so please
smoke as much as you would like.
You're amazing.
Now, while you're with us,
perhaps you would like to learn about
our village as well as our customs.
Studying and me don't get along, but
smoking and I do. Help me. Wait a minute.
We should be respectful. Uh.
Do not worry, Yaku.
We start off by harvesting
the grapes we grow.
We make wine out of the flesh
and all of the leaves are dried.
You must drive them in the
shade for three to six months.
Then remove the veins of the leaves.
They're cut carefully into small pieces
and
that is the
process of the creation.
Everyone in this village plays an
important part in making this tobacco.
Those who help grow it may smoke.
it as well.
Assisting us is key if
you'd like to partake.
What a stupid bull.
Can you try to be nice?
Your appreciation will
certainly bloom if you
help prepare the tobacco
with your own two hands.
Well then, now we work.
Not fair.
That looks horrible. I'm sorry.
Such is the way of things.
Ah, so good. Right?
This stuff's amazing.
We have few complaints.
It is the crown jewel of the village.
The rich aroma does make those...
Oh, gross!
Electronic cigarettes
are way better than this!
Hey, lady, maybe adding
some menthol would be good.
It would be easier to...
What the hell's wrong with you, Hame?
How dare you stink around
that way, you're back!
No, no, not everyone has
the same taste that we do.
It is simply not meant for her taste buds.
You're way more gel than
I figured you would be.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry for all of this, chief. All is well.
I take no offense.
Come look at this.
That is Mianolith.
For eons, our Alpha tribe has stood
watch over the god enshrined inside.
I thought it was just a big wall.
During the great conflict
of centuries past,
we could hear the solemn meow of our God,
but now we exist in silence.
When we prepare the tobacco,
we offer a prayer to the God.
We breathe prayer into
each chop of every leaf.
Chop means creator hear our prayers.
It reminds us to give thanks
often not only to our God,
but our ancestors for all of the
peace we have enjoyed on this planet.
Look our tattoos mean the same thing.
These two designs represent the Mianolith
constantly reaching toward the Sun
Whenever our hearts lose their way.
We look at these tattoos to
find the right path once more
It's a pee pee the tattoo.
A pee pee and a kooka!
Ah!
Chainsmoker Cat!
Settle down, Wynn.
Tryna light this bad boy.
This ritual is for the
criminals within our
village who seek redemption
from the Mianolith.
Look, from that edge, it is a small leap.
I've witnessed even children
complete this ritual.
We didn't sign up for this shit!
And I definitely don't trust this role!
You'll find the vines to be quite
durable and worthy of your use.
I'll die if I jump and I really,
really don't want to die!
The time for fear has passed.
Jump!
Well, if I fall from here, I'll die.
Are you afraid of dying?
There's a saying all in our village know.
Death should be kept close.
It is your friend.
I won't be able to smoke if I'm dead.
I'll give you a generous share of our
tobacco if you take the jump off of...
Any one of you got a lighter?
I've never met one like her.
Can she truly be without any fear?
Maybe this isn't actually
as bad as I thought.
Guys,
these crazy villagers
just told me that I'd
be killed if I didn't
jump off this big tower.
How mean.
I'm too adorable to die.
Seriously, it's a village of bullies.
Embrace fear.
Well, I must say all of your
jumps were quite impressive.
From this day forward, you
are part of our village.
you will always be welcome here
yeah I'm sure you'll see me soon
this stuff gets a 10.0 it's like
three days worth all rolled into one
it was Fun even with the hiccups we
should go back that's a no for me huh?
Why not the?
Alpha totally loved you you even got a
nickname the creator of rainbows that Video
view is I mean we have a ton of great
footage by the way what
is alpha Mean anyway?
What it's the first letter of
the Greek alphabet okay and
what does It mean I guess it's
something like the first one or
the beginning well that's Lame
you're gonna get shot with a
ray gun again hey guys we eat you
want to get before we go home?
I want Mabaroshiya's curry!
You shit your pants and you still
want to eat curry right now?
Hey, that's a lie!
I didn't shit my pants!
I call dips on the curry and beer.
Look!
The cicada!
They're gaming for her!
Look at you go, girl!
That was a crazy reaction.
Wow.
I need to wash the chopsticks.
Okay. Okay.
And why would you use chopsticks?
I seriously thought she was
going to eat that thing.
Imoko!
Here!
I brought some new ones!
You did?
Yeah, I got them from the cafeteria.
Oh, thank you.
Wait, you mean you walked all
the way over to the cafeteria?
Well, you know, you wouldn't want to keep
eating with your other chopsticks, right?
Yeah, you're right.
Man, you're purring a lot right now.
You going through puberty?
Let's go! No!
I was kidding.
Well, maybe you're right.
What the heck? That was gross.
You have to cook it first.
That was your problem with it?
It was good.
Tastes like shrimp.
The wind-lightened light,
the light-hearted light.
The light-hearted light, just the smoke.
I'm just sitting in a chair.
I'm drawing a picture of a mirror.
I'm bringing the light-hearted light.
I'm in a mirror.
I'm looking for a light-hearted light.
The light-hearted light is
not set to be the next door.
Yeah, I'm trying to make it.
Hey, sometimes the people who
are the people who are the same,
This is the end of the day?
I'm still here.
I'm not afraid of!
the wind.
I'm on the way.
It's raining.
I'm on the way Thank you.
Thank you.